here are eight steps to un your life
step one cleanse thy Earthly vessel
shower get fresh treat yourself with
respect brush your teeth wear a scent
because this is it this is the character
you're playing as and if you fail to
take care of yourself on a basic level
you'll fail outwards in space and time
because it all starts with you being
clean and feeling fresh as a ritual will
increase your self-perception over time
time you'll be putting your best foot
forward and will be signaling to your
subconscious that you're worth taking
care of so even if Yellow Stone erupts
and the world descends into chaos and
destruction at least you'll smell good
step two order the kingdom clean your
room deep clean your house get rid of
all the that's scattering your mind
refuse to live in a monument of Filth
like an everpresent reminder of things
left undone because the space you occupy
is an extension of yourself is it
disordered cuz if it is so are you so
take your pick you can order yourself or
order your kingdom it doesn't really
matter because it's the same thing no
more half-done jobs go room to room and
make things right make things beautiful
when you are clean and your kingdom is
too then you'll feel like you have your
together somewhat and it will
encourage you to bring that energy to
the rest of your life start with you and
the things that you have control over
and then Venture forth when you have
your ducks in a row then get out of the
house Rapunzel stayed in her Tower
because she was emotionally manipulated
by a devouring mother but what about you
the human brain operates best with our
feet moving sun in our face and eyes
moving from left to right go outside
because everyone's wondering where you
went we're meant to be in relationship
and Community with others become an
initiator of people coming together and
things happening because the modern
world is designed from the ground up to
keep you inside we technically don't
have to leave the house ever so a lot of
us don't and our lives pass Us by step
four sweat if I told you there was a
pill that was guaranteed to boost your
mental and physical energy throughout
the day increase your overall mood and
outlook on life improve your mental
Clarity prolong your life span and
increase your physical attractiveness
would you take that pill but that pill
is real and it's called working out and
the top performers in the world take it
every day so get the blood pumping go
break a sweat do it daily because that
which coste energy giveth energy step
five monitor thy treasury because giant
corporations are thriving on the fact
that you don't they encourage
unconscious spending and autor renewing
subscriptions that slowly bleed you of
your hard-earned cash and this out of
sight out of mind attitude is keeping
you stuck so check your balance daily
does it sting good let that sting
motivate you to investigate what's going
on what are you paying for that you
don't care about exposing yourself to
the hard numbers unlocks the ability to
do something about it step six remove
the hooks what are you bound to what are
you dependent on in order to operate at
Baseline what external substances or
behaviors are you using to medicate
internal problems turn off notifications
stop getting pulled back into the cycle
unsubscribe to email chains unfollow
Instagram accounts remove things that
constantly pull you back into mindless
consumerism step seven strategize every
military operation political campaign
major corporation relies on a strategy
to increase the chances of success if
you were tasked to run one of these
entities and you showed up without a
strategy you'd be laughed out the door
but what about your life are you just
floating through without a strategy
hoping you'll end up in a desirable
Place 5 years down the line well I'm
sorry to be the one to tell you but
things don't usually get better on their
own even a man of Faith would be a fool
not to be proactive with the tools God
has given him for is sloth not a sin so
put the figure on the board what do you
want in life and in what ways do you
tend to fail achieving it develop a
strategy based on the information you
have available and use this info to
figure out the most effective way
forward you'd be surprised as to how
monstrously effective even a basic
strategy can be step eight submit submit
to the things you must do because the
thinking has already been done by you
shut your mind off and relinquish
yourself of the the burden of
overthinking learn what it feels like to
put your rationalization on mute take a
deep breath and do what you need to do
trust the more authentic voice in your
head and let it override your weaker
self because over time this authentic
self will become your primary voice and
the more you listen to your authentic
self the more you will develop a
stronger sense of identity and having a
strong reliable identity is the basis of
confidence and self self- efficacy and
there's no better feeling than that so
if you're beaten and battered and tired
from The Strife then follow these eight
steps and un your
life thank you to athletic greens for
sponsoring this video ag1 is the
simplest way to keep your mind and body
energized optimized and focused
throughout the day you guys know that
ag1 is by far my favorite supplement and
that's because there's no competing with
its nutritional profile and since it's
sourced from Whole Foods it's extremely
bioavailable which means when you drink
ag1 your body can actually absorb and
use all of the nutrients and vitamins
instead of urinating it out like so many
cheaper multivitamins so staying healthy
and mentally sharp is as easy as it's
ever been so if you're interested in
joining me in this daily
self-optimization Health habit then if
you use my link in the description below
you'll get a year supply of the vitamin
D3 and K 2 complex which I also have
every single morning as well as five ag1
travel packs with your first purchase so
make sure to take advantage of my link
below and thanks again athletic greens
for sponsoring this video if you liked
this video it would be a huge help if
you hit the like button because when you
hit the like button the algorithm
blesses me and it shoves my head into
other people's home pages helping them
out which also helps me out so it's just
a win-win for everybody involved if you
hit the like button if you're lurking
here consider subscribing also check out
the inaction as a slow death merch over
on better ideas.com so many of you are
purchasing it we're almost running out
so grab yours before they're gone other
than that thank you so much for watching
and we'll catch you in the next video